Downloaded from
Official YIFY movies site:
Terrifying images are
coming in now of an unknown object.
We fear the thousands
trapped inside may already be dead.
Traffic out of the evacuation zone
is at a complete standstill.
- So what do you think it is?
- Aliens.
- Definitely aliens.
- That is the finger of God!
They're saying
it's some kind of mineral formation.
Capturing the moment the object,
known as the Spike, disappeared.
Has reappeared 50 miles off
the coast of Busan, South Korea.
Who wants it here in Texas?
Responsible for numerous
strange phenomena.
Mass satellite failure resulting.
Crop failure across
agricultural regions around the world.
Deadly rioting continues.
Over 100 million dead.
We keep dying, and they're doing nothing!
Happy birthday, baby girl.
It's okay.
Son of a bitch!
Nope. Okay, it's fine.
Where are you? Come on, come on.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Call all you want, assholes,
I still don't have any money.
What the fuck? How are you so long?
How are you so long?
Thalia, I think it's the bank.
Yeah, she's right here.
Hello?
Oh, that's so weird.
Sorry, yeah, I've been by my phone
all day. I didn't hear it ring once.
Yes, ma'am. I have a job.
I'm packing up my truck
right now to go first thing tomorrow
to California with my bees. I'm...
Okay. Well, I don't control
when almonds are pollinated,
so you're gonna get a big fat
check in about two weeks, okay? Goodbye!
Honey, if you need some help...
Please, Dad, it's not like you and
Mom have money to spare. I'll be fine.
I meant help packing up.
We could have a little time
to hang out and--
Dad, I don't need help, okay?
I know this is a hard day for you,
so I really appreciate you
letting us visit them.
- It meant a lot to everybody.
- Dad, stop!
Maybe next time clean around the graves.
It's disrespectful.
Okay, come on, girls.
Let's get you packed.
God, you got heavy.
What has Mama been feeding you?
I'm gonna get you on a bee diet.
Diet for bees.
This is gonna take all night.
What the fuck?
- Morning, Kai. Did I wake you?
- Really, Jenna?
That was a good speech you gave
at Dave's funeral.
- It was beautiful.
- What are you doing out here?
It's been a week since you
ghosted everyone, dude.
Look, I know you need some space,
but you can only skip work
so long before they fire you.
Whatever.
I can't afford my place now
that Dave's out of the picture.
So what, Dave's car is gonna be
your new permanent residence?
Well, it will be, since I can't move it.
- Kai.
- Now unboot me, please.
You gotta clean this shit up.
You're lucky I don't give you a ticket.
For what?
Uh, littering, loitering,
illegally parked vehicle, open container.
- Ah, that is piss.
- Oh.
Kai, I love you, but you need to stop
coming back here. It's not good for you.
Bring my boot back tonight.
Love you too, sis.
I'm tired.
Stop falling asleep, stupid bitch.
No!
Fuck!
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
- Hey, lady, you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm so sorry. That was my fault. I was
just parked in the middle of the road.
No, it's okay. I should have been paying
more attention to you.
- Can you help me with this, actually?
- Yeah, sure.
I'm just gonna adjust these straps
and then can you ratchet it down
when I tell you to?
- Okay.
- Okay, ratchet.
Okay, great. Thank you.
- Oh!
- You okay?
Yeah, sorry. Shit.
I think I just bumped my knee
when I rolled into the...
ditch.
- Sorry again about this.
- Oh, it's fine.
Oh, my God, I didn't ask if you were okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Uh, yeah, not a scratch on me.
- Kai, by the way.
- I'm, uh, Thalia.
Sorry, I was just worried
about my-- My bees.
- Yeah, beekeeping, huh?
- They're fine.
- That's pretty neat.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, can I look at your leg?
- What?
- Oh, it's cool. I'm an EMT.
Oh! Uh...
- No, I'm fine.
- It just looked like you bumped
your knee pretty hard.
Oh, no. It's probably just a bruise.
- Are you sure?
- Fucking hell! What?
Oh, my God, it's broken.
Oh, no, it's just swelling.
It's just a little swelling.
- You sit here, okay?
- Okay.
I'll get my kit. I'll be right back, okay?
You're gonna be fine.
- Sit tight.
- Oh, my God.
That's so big.
Oh, shit.
Got it. Don't poke at it.
Are you sure it's not broken?
If it was broken,
you wouldn't be able to walk on it.
Hey, that's-- Whoa! That's tight,
that's tight, that's too tight.
It's gotta be, trust me.
Okay?
Okay.
It doesn't look too bad,
so we'll just wrap this up nice and tight
and keep it from getting worse.
Right...
- Nice calves.
- Hm?
What?
Did you say something?
I said, um...
I said, um, do you--
Do I need to ice my calves later?
This is your knee.
Yep.
You know, leg, knee,
calf, it's all the same.
I mean, you're the doctor, so...
Well, EMT's are technically not doctors.
Really? What are you?
Well, we basically
know everything they do,
but we get paid less
and get to run through red lights.
Oh.
Was that your ambulance then?
I mean, it could be if you wanted it.
Excuse me?
- Just trying to make a joke.
- Uh...
- I didn't really hear a joke in there.
- Yeah, I was just messing around.
I don't know, it kind of sounded more like
you were using your cool car
to try to, I don't know, hit on me.
Hm?
- No, I wasn't, I swear.
- Okay.
It's not even my car.
It's my dead friend's car,
and I wouldn't bring up my dead friend
in order to flirt with you, okay?
Anyway.
You're good to go.
That sucks about your friend.
Yeah, well, it happens.
Like, all the time now, right?
Now, he was the cool one.
Hence the car.
He would have definitely flirted with you.
Well, he probably
couldn't have fixed my leg.
No, he could have. He was a doctor.
Well, um, I should probably get going.
I've got a long drive.
Yeah, right. Um...
- Well, safe drive, Thalia.
- Yeah, you too.
Friend.
- It's Kai.
- Yeah, I know.
I was just trying to be friendly.
I don't know.
Here, I'll tell you what.
Catch.
Huh.
Honey.
Thanks for the help, doc.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God, where did they go?
Where did they go?
What the fuck?
Oh, my God, where are they?
Where's the trailer?
- Where did they go?
- No! No!
You son of a bitch! No!
What is this? What is this?
- What the actual shit?
- Oh, my God, the Spike jumped.
- It was right here.
- The Spike jumped.
It did this. It must have.
Oh, no!
- Okay.
- Where did it go? No!
- You were right here.
- Okay.
- Okay, so--
- What the fuck?
Okay, so--
It looks like, like, two pieces of land
got swapped somehow.
What? The Spike can't do that, can it?
Have you ever heard of that happening?
So if this is-- If the land got swapped,
then maybe the chunk
that had all of our stuff...
This looks like a river,
so maybe it's nearby.
- Maybe it's nearby.
- Yeah! Yeah!
I know there's a river on the other side
of those hills, so maybe--
Yeah, it's gotta be! Okay!
Let's do this! Yeah!
Fuck, these aren't Arizona trees.
Are you okay?
- Jesus!
- This is all shit!
There is a god and he hates us!
Ow!
I cut my hand!
Dude, can you get up, please?
We need to figure this out.
Okay. Maybe this is Florida?
And that is a fish. Why is there a fish?
Hey, I found something.
- What is it?
- Pizza place. In Eastern WA.
Washington's like 19 hours away.
Okay. I can still make it.
I can still make it.
- Yeah. Better get a move on.
- Exactly. Thanks, Kai.
It's locked.
Uh, what are you doing?
Oh, right. Mud man over here. Do you have,
like, a spare shirt or something?
- No, you're not getting in here.
- What?
Of course I am.
Just give me a second to clean up.
Sorry.
Do you think you're coming
to Washington with me?
Yeah, I am. My car's gone too.
No, no, no. I will call you
if I find the car, but no, dude.
You're going to ditch me
on the side of the goddamn road?
- Okay.
- I found the clue. I found the bottle.
Look, I'm not going on a road trip
with a total stranger
who, frankly, seems a little
emotionally unstable. So...
Okay, look. I'm sorry.
It's just that car is the last thing
I have of my best friend, okay?
It's important to me.
Look, something crazy
just happened to the both of us.
And we're the only people
who can help each other right now.
Please.
I'm sorry. I just have...
I have to find a phone
and call the farm and tell them
I'm gonna be late and--
Oh, the fucking bank
keeps calling me and I just...
I have too much shit
on my plate right now. I'm sorry.
How can I contact you?
Here.
I'm also a DJ.
Please call me if you find that car.
I will. I promise.
Or if you need a shitty DJ.
Goddamn it, Thalia.
What are you doing? Just fucking...
Just go. He's a grown man.
He's safe out here.
You don't have to worry about him.
It's 20 minutes to a gas station,
he's fine. He's a stranger.
It's safer not to do it.
It's safer not to do it, just...
It's not even that hot outside.
He could just--
Okay, fuck it. Fuck it.
Do the right thing.
- Let the stranger in to your car.
- Shit.
- You'll probably get murdered.
- Shit, no.
Kai! Come back! You can come with me!
- Where the fuck did he go?
- Oh, fuck.
Kai?
Come on, don't be like that.
Are you coming or what?
Kai?
Yeah, looks like you've got
a hole in your truck.
Pretty big one too.
I'm gonna stop at the next gas station
and you can get some paper towels
and clean up back there.
Hey, you got any mediums back here?
Would you just take
whatever's in there, please?
Uh, yeah, you got it.
- Do you want this open or shut?
- What?
- The window.
- I don't care.
Uh, okay.
- This stupid thing's kind of stuck.
- Just leave it.
- Just leave it!
- I got it.
Sorry.
You don't need to get a new beekeeper.
I will be there on Tuesday.
A 20% cut seems a little steep
for just being a couple days late.
You're--
I-- I hear you, but you're not going to be
behind schedule. It's not--
Yes, but I promise you,
it's not going to be a problem.
Look, my bees are going to be so goddamn
horny for your almonds,
I'm not going to be able to pull them off!
Yes, yeah, I apologize.
Yes, that was unprofessional. I'm just--
I'm just very proud of my bees.
Yes, a 20% cut does seem fair.
Okay. I will see you Tuesday. Bye.
What?
That's a lot of mud.
Fuck!
Fuck. My leg, bro!
Dude, this car hit me!
Oh, dude, my leg's broken. Fuck.
Bro, you ran over my bro!
- Hunter, you good, dog?
- My leg's fucked up!
I got to get you to a hospital, dog.
Looks like this fuckwad's going to pay.
The car wasn't even on.
Yeah, but no one knows that,
so who are they going to believe?
Look, if it's cash that you want,
I don't have any.
Shit!
I told you he was poor.
We've been stuck here for hours, dude.
Let's just go back.
I hear you, man, but we're not going back
to the darkness, you feel?
- I feel.
- You know why, right?
Because I'm your light?
- Damn right! And what does light do?
- Go forward.
- Yes! We hit it!
- Let's go!
- I love you, bro.
- I love you more, bro.
My dog forever.
Can I get a full tank on three and this?
This doughnut's kind of stale.
Can I get a discount?
Absolutely not.
- But it's really hard.
- Can I see?
What do you mean, can you see?
What are you doing?
- Don't bite it!
- That's fine.
Why would you take a bite of it?
Because it's fine.
I said, "Mom, I'm not
gonna pay rent. This is my room."
No, then my mom told me to get a job
or get out. So we got out.
I called my gramps and he said if we get
to him, we could chill at his place.
Yeah, but we got a flat,
so we need some cash for a patch.
And, you know, we Gucci.
But where are you guys, like, headed?
Like, maybe we could give you a lift
or something.
He's in Vermont, so, like, I don't know.
- Wait, what?
- Vermont.
Yeah, but you know that's
like 2,000 miles away, right?
Yeah, that's why we need 5 bucks
to fix his tire.
Dudes, I know your moms are, like,
bummers or whatever, but...
- No, my mom's cool.
- Yeah, his mom said he doesn't need a job.
Fine, whatever, but, like,
do you guys have, like, supplies
or train tickets or anything?
We got our bikes.
Yo, and Brody's got my back.
Come here, Brody.
Give me one of those.
You guys know if you do this,
you're going to die, right?
Dog, that big dick in the sky
could nut us any sec.
Yeah, that's what happened
to my mom's boyfriend,
which was a bummer
because, you know, my dad sucks balls.
Are you guys, like, not scared?
Man, we just two down-end homies
on a journey towards a better life.
I love you, dog.
Yeah, I get it.
I had a homie.
Damn, dog.
Was he nutted?
Mm. No.
I mean, he's dead, but...
- Dude, I'm sorry, dude.
- You don't have to say it like that.
I'm sorry about that, dog.
I'll tell you what.
You guys do me a solid.
If you clean the back of the truck,
I will get you the patch
and some supplies to go with it.
- How about that?
- Let's go!
- Yeah!
- I appreciate that.
- Yeah, of course, of course, of course.
"Palouse River."
That is a long-ass river.
I'm gonna get you on the road.
Oh, hey. Check it.
So I found the river, and there's
only a couple of towns near it.
Our stuff's got to be around there.
I feel like that's our best bet.
- Oh, great. Good job.
- Thanks.
Yeah, so I promised Hunter and Brody
that I would get this for them if they
would just, like, clean up the truck.
Is that okay?
I don't... Who is that?
Oh, just some fellow travelers
in need of some help.
Okay. You can go buy it for them, then.
Yeah, well, I was wondering
if maybe you could get it
because I don't have any money.
You don't have any money?
Well, I did.
I mean, in Dave's car, I had a lot of
money and, you know, vanished, so...
- That was a lie. Yeah.
- It was a lie, yeah.
Look, come on. It's a couple of bucks.
I can't spare the cash, man.
Look, they're just really good guys,
and I really like them, and...
Little shits!
- No, no, no!
- No!
- It's got no gas, they can't get very far.
- All right, wait up!
You're such an idiot.
You're the one who left
the keys in the engine.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Stupid. I'm tired.
Oh, goddammit, I'm so out of shape.
Just give me the good bike.
- I'll catch up with them.
- Hell no!
Have it your way.
Eat my entire ass!
Don't hate me because I'm in great shape.
Whoa!
- Enjoy the walk, bitch.
- That's my lumbar.
It's never gonna heal.
Hey, don't leave without me!
Hey!
Oh, I'm only 34.
Our generation aged so fucking fast.
Shit. I'm so tired.
I'm so tired all the time. Fuck.
- Fuck.
- Get on the back.
Oh, God, fine. Okay.
Okay.
You better not drop me,
you fucking asshole.
Okay, I'm ready. Let's do this!
The moon is so bright, dog.
- Yeah, dog.
- You shitheads!
- Yo, your truck's out of gas.
- I thought we were bros!
- Hey, where's my bike?
- I threw that shit away!
- God, you're such a mom.
- Off.
- Off the car!
- You owe me, like, another bike.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Yeah, get the fuck out of here.
- Let's ditch these moms, dude.
- Yeah, let's go to Vermont.
Vermont?
Yeah.
- You are biking to Vermont?
- Yeah, my pop-pop's chill as fuck.
He's got guns and shit, no cap.
Children, if you do this,
you will not make it.
- Do you understand? You will die.
- Hey, lady, living is dying.
Yeah, and we're gonna live biking
towards what we want.
GYAT's in the guest house.
You two are the dumbest motherfuckers
I've ever met.
Whatever.
Rather get nutted
because we did something dumb...
Than get nutted doing nothing
'cause we're dumb.
- Chew on that, mom.
- Don't call me mom.
Yeah, get out of here.
It's just me and you, Brody.
Forever, man. For life, okay?
You guys are gonna get nutted, dog.
Nutting is like what they call it
when the Spike kills someone.
Not, you know...
I want to go to bed.
We'll get more gas tomorrow.
Okay.
Stupid shitheads.
Come on.
Are you jerking off in my truck?
- What?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
No, I'm just...
I'm going to sleep.
- Sorry, I didn't mean to wake you.
- It's okay. Good night.
It's just little things
have been setting me off lately.
And, uh, I saw your kid's drawings
and your photo.
You never mentioned
you had a family, so I just...
I assumed the worst.
My friend's funeral was like
two weeks ago, so I guess I'm just...
Seeing death everywhere.
Yeah.
Your family's okay, right?
Um...
My husband and daughter died
six years ago.
Please don't, Kai.
- I'm being so rude.
- No, you're not.
I'm just-- Sorry, just give me a minute.
Ow.
No, Kai, we don't-- It's not--
- Just one second.
- Let's just go to sleep, huh?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to bring all that up.
Please continue.
I was saying we should go to sleep.
Right, yeah.
Can I ask you a question?
Uh, yeah, go ahead.
Does it get easier?
Yeah. It gets easier.
That's good.
Dave was really good
at shrugging stuff off. I could--
I could never get the hang of it.
You know, when the Spike hit,
I sort of spiraled out of control.
Yeah, I think a lot of people did.
Yeah.
The world was going insane,
and I was staring at patient charts
and doing paperwork.
It didn't make any sense, so I quit.
Dave was the only reason
that I ended up as a paramedic, at least.
He kept me from
totally going off the rails.
Sorry. Here.
Let me give this back to you.
You know he built that car?
He's not even a car guy.
One day he just bought a roller
and pieced it together from scratch.
It took him years.
You know, we were gonna go on this road
trip to celebrate it finally being done.
Sorry.
I'm rambling.
It's just, I really thought
he had his shit together.
But I guess not.
And if he didn't, then...
How did he die?
He killed himself.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
I guess I just assumed it was the Spike.
It must make it a lot harder.
Spike, suicide.
Dead is dead.
What about your family?
Spike?
Um...
No. Uh, it was a car crash.
Fuck.
Yeah, semi just, you know...
ran into oncoming traffic.
It was like a wrong place,
wrong time kind of thing, but, um...
But it was instantaneous, so...
No, it wasn't. I don't...
I don't fucking know
why I always say that.
I guess it's to make it easier
for other people.
It wasn't instantaneous, but I...
got to say goodbye to my daughter,
so there's that.
Anyway.
History.
Just gotta let go of the things
that hurt you.
That's like everything nowadays.
Just find something that keeps you going
and hang on to that.
Is that beekeeping for you?
Does that keep you happy?
I didn't say happy.
I'd be pretty arrogant to aim
for happiness right now,
but it does keep me going.
I don't know.
I still think it's okay
to aim for some happiness.
Well, I hope you find some.
Me too.
As in, I hope you do as well.
Well, if you really want to make me happy,
you'll go the fuck to sleep.
- I need to go to sleep.
- Copy that.
Hey.
Thanks for listening.
Fuck it! God-fucking-damn it!
Morning.
Yeah.
- So we've got, like, 14--
- How's the swelling?
- Oh, sorry. Your leg.
- What?
Did the swelling go down?
Uh, yeah. It's fine. Um...
We've got a long drive to Washington,
and we probably
should have left an hour ago.
- Right.
- You're up first.
Aye, aye, captain.
I'll just go drain the main vein.
Drain the main vein?
Who the fuck says that?
Hey, do you like 20 questions?
Because I'm kind of a beast at it.
Um, I don't really like games.
Oh, that's cool.
We could just chat.
Like, what's your favorite album?
Me, I have a few,
but it really just depends on my mood.
I need to sleep before my shift, Kai.
- You're gonna sleep?
- Yes.
Oh, come on!
Shooting the shit
is the best part of road trips.
Me and Dave, we just talk, talk,
talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk.
Look, Kai, I'm not Dave, okay?
This is not some fun trip for me.
It's work.
Okay.
Fine.
Of course, you're not Dave.
Talk to not Dave.
In fact, nowadays,
we only talk to not Daves.
I'm sorry.
Let's just, you know,
focus on the mission.
Right?
You're right. Sorry.
The mission. Got it.
- You got any music or anything?
- Radio's busted.
That's cool.
Kai, what are you doing?
That's so annoying.
- Sorry. Did I wake you?
- No, but what are you doing?
Well, I'm making a smoke bubble
in my mouth.
- Have you never done that?
- I have no idea what you're saying.
Like the science experiment.
With the clouds in the bottles?
You can do it with your mouth. Watch this.
Okay, it didn't really work that time.
- When it happens--
- I'm going back to sleep.
All right.
Screw it. I got one.
- Got what?
- I have a thing for 20 questions.
- You want to play 20 questions?
- Oh, okay. Uh...
- Is it an animal?
- Yes.
Is it a bee?
Buh, buh, buh, buh!
- Oh, my God. Wow!
- You got it.
- That was the quickest I've ever done it.
- Oh my God. Mmm.
Okay, my turn.
Okay, hold on.
So it's smaller than a paper clip.
- And it's medium furry?
- Mm-hm.
- Nineteen. Last one.
- What the--
Goddamn it, is it a fucking bee?
Oh, don't smile at me, you cheater.
Piece of shit.
Okay, here we go.
Sushi.
- I want to eat sushi now.
- I don't get why we can't eat it anymore.
Something to do with, like,
the way that the Spike interacts
with heavy metals in the ocean
or something. I don't know.
Like it makes it poisonous, I guess.
- Fuck the CDC.
- Honestly, I don't give a fuck.
- I would eat it. I would still eat it.
- Me either. I would eat that shit all day.
This is our exit, 89 North.
Wait, isn't it safer
to cut across through Nevada?
Yeah, but we're sticking to main roads
and we're not stopping anywhere, so...
This will be faster.
- Well, this goes through New Zion, right?
- Yeah.
- And across to Glass Lake.
- Yes.
- Why are you asking? What's the problem?
- Nothing, no. I just, um...
Dave wanted to see the Glass Lake.
It was, like,
his number one spot on the list.
Have you seen it? Is it cool?
Uh, it's a large lake of glass
where a bunch of people died,
if that's cool to you.
Yeah, right.
We can't go around it,
so are you going to be okay?
I'm good. Why?
- Really?
- I'm not going to cry again.
Look, I'll probably just, like,
sleep through it or something.
No, I should look at it.
Dave wanted to see it, so I should...
I'll be fine. We'll be fine. I'm fine.
Great.
I wonder why Dave
wanted to see this so bad.
I probably should have asked him.
- Whoa, Thalia!
- Sorry. Sorry.
- All I'm saying is, I don't think--
- Can we not when--?
Never mind. Keep going, it's fine.
I'm not saying I want to kill to survive,
but, like, I gotta pay rent
and bills and shit.
Like, we're out here because
you need to pay your mortgage, right?
Yeah.
I don't think anyone expected
the end of civilization to be so normal.
That's normal to you?
- Well, it was just pissing, like we do.
- Oh, I hate that.
- Come on.
- Just turn it off.
- You're not going to find something.
- I'm going to find something.
You just need to be a little patient, please.
Did I break it?
- Those are footsteps.
- They're getting closer.
- Yeah!
- Jesus.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- What the--?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah!
- Oh, he's still going.
- Oh!
- That's it?
- That was amazing.
- He's insane.
- He's not insane.
He's just living his best life.
I'm sorry. It kind of sounds like you
kind of want to be like Yeah Man.
Hell yeah, I do.
You want to broadcast
your dumb life on the radio?
Well, I wouldn't do that personally, but,
you know, I would do something like that.
Like what?
- Live my life on the open road.
- Okay.
I mean, maybe it's a little selfish,
but my plan right now is to get
the car back and just drift around.
No destination, no rules.
Just get away from everything
and everyone.
Hm. Nothing wrong
with being a little selfish.
Right?
I mean, I haven't told anyone my plan.
Not my sister, not my friends.
You're the only person who knows.
Sometimes it's easier
to talk to people you don't know.
True.
- They don't judge you.
- Oh, I'm judging you.
- I think you're as weird as Yeah Man.
- He's not weird.
Yes, he is. You're just weird too,
so you can't see it.
You milk bugs for a living.
I don't milk. Do you think bees are--?
I'm sorry, do you...?
Where do you think honey comes from?
- Their udders.
- I can't believe you're an EMT.
They have found hives that are,
no joke, over 100 years old.
As long as some of the bees survive,
the hive just keeps going.
Really?
Kind of like, um, do you know,
like, sourdough starter?
- Yeah.
- You can take that sourdough starter
and make a bunch of bread with it,
but the original starter,
- it just goes on forever.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- So, in a way, bees live forever.
Yeah, kind of.
I guess the hive does, or it can.
So what happens when the queen dies?
That's the craziest part.
They can just make new queens.
- What?
- I know!
So, basically, they just have
this thing called royal jelly,
and then they feed it to any bee,
and that bee goes from living like a month
to living three to five years.
- That is crazy.
- It just goes to show,
any bitch can be a queen
if you feed her right.
You need to put that on a shirt.
Fuck, that's such a good idea.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Do you know what's going on here?
Some park ranger just rolled by and said
it's backed up because of cult shit.
They're having some big bonfire
and feast or something.
Do you know how long this might take?
The ranger said they usually wait
till nightfall to clear them out,
so I'd get comfortable.
Okay, I found a back road.
- It's better than waiting here.
- Wait, the back roads? You sure?
I mean, maybe it'll clear up
sooner than they think.
Can't waste time. Gotta go.
Gotta go! The bees can't wait forever.
Hopefully we can get there before
nightfall so we can actually support--
- What was that?
- Shit.
Yeah, it's definitely shredded.
Oh, you need a hand?
- And the spare's flat.
- What? How?
- From the last time I had a flat.
- Right. Well, maybe we can push it.
I'm so fucking stupid. Why didn't I wait?
Why didn't I just fucking wait?
Hey, you're not stupid, okay?
We'll figure it out.
- We can maybe drive on it.
- To where?
We're out in the middle of nowhere
and we're miles from the main road.
Okay, we could use duct tape.
I think I saw some duct tape in the back.
You know, just duct tape it
and we can just push it
- and it'll get us to the road at least.
- Kai, come on.
- Where are you going?
- Come on!
- They seem like the self-sufficient type.
- They might have an air compressor.
Yeah, and a stockpile of ammo.
- Are you sure you want to do this?
- I don't have a choice.
We can't be stuck
in the middle of nowhere.
Yeah, exactly.
No help, no witnesses,
nowhere to find our bodies.
Look, I'm okay.
If you want to go back, it's okay.
You can go. I'm fine.
We need to fix the tire, okay?
I just don't want to get shot.
Well, then just be quiet
and look, I don't know, friendly.
Shit!
Thalia, stay low. I'll draw that fire.
What? Kai!
Hey, you fucks!
Let me see if you can hit this, huh?
- Kai, get down!
- Thalia, run!
- Get down!
- Thalia, get out of here!
You can't shoot me, can you, cocksucker?
Shut your mouth, shit stick.
That was just a warning shot.
Now get off my land!
Um...
Hi.
Sorry.
Our tire just blew out up the road
and we were wondering
if you had an air compressor.
Yeah, of course I got one.
Oh, okay, great.
Would you mind if we--?
Nobody comes to these back roads
unless they're looking for trouble.
Now I'm going to count to three and these
next shots won't be warning shots.
It's just going to take a second.
Just a minute and then we'll be gone.
I don't help militia or meth heads.
- Why?
- Lady, I'm just a beekeeper.
And I'm unemployed. Not because of meth.
Uh, I quit. Not meth.
I've never done meth. I quit my job.
- He's never done meth.
- I'm on a--
- Did you say a beekeeper?
- Yeah, that's what she said.
Why, do you need one?
Hello, little ladies. Don't mind me.
See, she ain't getting stung.
What were you doing?
Don't worry,
she's a professional beekeeper.
Don't talk to my kid.
Hey, you want to see something cool?
- There's nothing to be afraid of.
- Oh, Thalia, don't talk to the kids.
She can.
You can't.
Come here, it's okay.
Go on, you heard the lady.
Don't worry.
If we're calm, they'll be calm.
And they won't sting us.
See?
You see this?
This is the queen.
Pretty cool, huh?
I know those bees seem scary,
but it was only because
they were trying to protect her.
And wherever she goes, they go too.
So you stay here,
I'm going to show you something cool.
Okay, stay right here.
Sorry in advance, little ladies.
You see that?
They're all going in the hive box,
because they know their queen's in there.
Those ones with their little butts up
and flapping their wings,
they're spreading her scent.
And then they're all going to get
to work gathering pollen,
and then they make wax cones
so they have a place
for all that delicious honey.
It's going to be their new home.
Pretty cool, huh?
Um, It'll take a couple hours
for them to hole up,
and then you can put them wherever.
That was so cool.
Seeing you in your element, really.
And plunging your hands into a pile of
bees was the craziest shit I've ever seen.
It's not a big deal.
Did you see that kid?
She thought you were a supey.
- Are you done yet?
- I'm going as fast as I can.
Well, go fucking faster.
Okay, I'm almost done. It's all good.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's not okay.
- Oh, God. I have to get this stuff.
- Thalia?
- It's going to be nice.
- You okay?
- It's going to be fine.
- Hey.
- It's going to be there.
- Thalia. Hey, hey, hey.
- I'm okay. It's okay.
- Thalia? It's okay.
Hey, sit down, sit down.
You're okay, you're okay.
Thalia, breathe, breathe.
You're having a panic attack, okay?
Just breathe with me.
You're going to be okay.
- I'm so fucking stupid.
- No, no, no.
- Why'd I do this?
- Thalia, just breathe.
- I'm going to lose the house.
- Just breathe.
- Breathe with me. You're okay.
- I'm going to lose them.
You're okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
Friday was my daughter's birthday.
My parents and my in-laws came over to...
I don't know, celebrate, grieve.
She liked bugs.
I think she would've liked beekeeping.
I'm sorry.
What are you gonna do?
Come on. Let's go.
Seriously, I'm okay.
This is not my first rodeo.
But thank you.
Hey, it's my job, right?
It was your job.
Was it? You get fired? What happened?
Are you still an EMT?
- Nah, I've definitely been fired.
- Should've been a combat medic.
- With all your zigzagging around.
- Pretty good, right?
There's only one more town around here,
but this road runs parallel to the river,
so I don't know.
Maybe it's a roadside pizza place
or something?
Maybe in the morning
we can find a local and ask them.
It's kind of too dark.
That's it, right?
These cozy, small-town vibes.
- I hate it.
- Yep.
Here it is.
So much for the best 'za
in Eastern WA.
Come on, let's just look for the river.
I think I see something in here.
Kai, what are you doing?
What are you--? Don't go. Kai!
What? Damn it. Kai.
- Jeez!
- I'm sorry, Kai.
I didn't get very far,
but look, I found the same bottle.
Okay. We're already here.
We need to find the river.
Right, yeah.
What was that?
I don't know,
maybe like a possum or something?
- Have you ever heard a possum before?
- No.
- Fuck, shit.
- What the hell was that?
I don't know.
Turn off your light. Turn off your light.
- Jackpot!
- Fuck.
This looks like a good one.
You folks in there, want to come see it?
Uh, excuse me?
Still, a 1990.
- Old one.
- Serial killer.
It's worth a look.
Not the oldest one I got,
but still pretty old for a penny.
Does he look crazy?
Thalia, what are you doing?
If you find anything in there from 1914,
let me know.
It's the only one I got missing.
Uh, we're not looking for coins.
- Is that what you're doing?
- Yeah, it's what I do nowadays.
Used to live here, me and my mom.
She got the lung cancer now.
Dad died when the town did.
Oh, I'm, uh, sorry to hear that. Uh...
This might be a weird question,
but you haven't happened to see
like a bunch of bees somewhere?
Or a Nissan 300ZX?
It's a sports car. Maybe in the river.
Nope. Can't say that I have.
I would know, though.
I've been up and down the river all week.
Where are you folks from?
- Uh, Arizona.
- Arizona? Check this.
- You know, we should probably go.
- Ta-da!
Wheat Penny, 1912.
- Oh.
- Oh, that's very old.
1912.
The year Arizona became a state.
- Right.
That means that this little penny
has been floating around
all these years
and found its way into my hands.
And now into yours, Arizona lady.
Thank you.
I got another one
in a little better condition.
We should probably get going, right?
- Yeah, right.
- I understand.
I should probably get home to my mom.
She don't talk much.
Not like you two chatterboxes.
Her throat hurts something fierce.
"More tea, please."
That's about what our conversation is.
God bless her, though.
Strongest, sweetest woman I know.
Tea and pennies don't sound like much,
but I figure some folks got less.
Anyway, I wish you guys the best of luck
with finding what you're looking for.
Penny Man is a really good
serial killer name.
Sir, wait.
Here. Um...
This is the good stuff,
especially the buckwheat.
This is from a couple of hives
on the edge of my farm.
And it's really good in tea,
so your mom should love it.
That's just real nice of you.
It's from both of us.
Thalia's Bee Sweet Honey. That's a hoot.
I'll be.
I saw that. I thought it was a turtle.
Where did you find this?
Campground about a half hour from here.
Real nice place.
Could you, um...? could you show us where?
Yeah, right there.
That's a little far from here.
That's not even on the main river.
- We would have never found this place.
- No.
I'm glad I talked to that guy.
That was nice of you, by the way.
- Giving him that honey?
- All right.
Let's go to bed.
I got an early start tomorrow.
Seriously.
- You're a nice person.
- Please.
You know, I was thinking when he left,
I should have charged him.
No, you didn't.
Just like you weren't going to leave me
on the side of the road.
Okay, fine, you caught me.
I'm a nice person.
And nice people deserve to be happy.
You should give yourself
a break sometimes.
You should give your back a break,
you geezer.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
One fall from a bike and I am ruined.
That's what it means to be an old man.
Good night.
- Kai?
- Yeah.
- This is stupid. Just sleep back here.
- What? No.
Wait. Yeah?
We can both fit back here. Come on.
Oh.
Okay, how do you want to do this?
Feet to head, head to feet?
I'm not sleeping with your feet
in my face. It's gross.
Right.
Okay, well, uh...
Are you 12? Don't make it weird.
Just lay down.
Don't get your hopes up.
Nothing's going to happen.
I literally just said don't make it weird.
Sorry.
- Kai, what are you doing?
- I'm just getting under the blanket.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
- Okay, I'm getting there.
- Stop.
I'm sorry.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
What are you doing?
Just, it's a bit loose.
Cool. Can we handle that tomorrow, please?
- Sure.
- Great.
Thank you. Good night.
Oh, my God. What is happening?
There is, like, a metal ring
or something stuck in my back.
Oh, it's just the carabiner, probably.
Just unhook it.
- The what?
- What do you mean the what?
It's a carabiner.
What is it doing?
It just keeps the mattress
from shifting around.
Just unclick it.
- Unclick it?
- Yes.
It's... I can't find it.
- What do you mean you can't?
- It is so dark in here.
Oh, my God, move.
Oh, my God.
See?
Better?
Yeah, much.
You made it weird.
Honk, honk.
Now it's weird.
Good night.
Oh, my God. What's that?
What is it? Did you hear that?
- What is that?
- Come on, slugabug.
- Get up.
- What?
Up, up, up.
What the fuck? What the fuck?
The farm is like 18 hours away,
so if I leave by sundown,
I should make it.
It's cutting it close, right?
I'll just have to drive all night,
load up on coffee or something.
Tell you what, I'll follow you.
If I see you drifting off,
I'll lay on my horn.
Oh, what a gentleman.
You gonna escort me the whole way?
Sure.
I've always wanted to go to California.
And after that?
I don't know. See where the road takes me.
Thalia, the river.
- Come on. Follow me. Hurry up.
- Kai! Where are you going?
- Upstream.
- Oh, right.
Yeah.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Follow me. Hurry up.
What? Yeah.
- Come on,
- Hurry up. I see red. I see red.
It's here.
Oh! Oh.
Fuck.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Fuck.
You're actually here.
Oh! Oh, you're here.
Okay, okay. I really found you.
I can't believe we found you.
God, you're a little stuck. It's fine.
We're going to get you out of here.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Maybe a few drifted down the river,
we could go check.
Is there anything salvageable?
Queen's still here.
I know it's just one bee,
but it's sourdough, right?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
It's not your fault.
This thing fucked us, should've known
the river would be a river.
What a fucking waste.
- Hey, where are you going?
- I gotta call the farm.
Tell them I'm not coming,
that should be a quick conversation.
Why would you kick it in?
I'm not dragging a wet box back.
- Yeah, but you killed the--
- Kai, will you just leave it?
Yeah, sure.
I can get home by tonight.
Try and convince the bank
not to foreclose on me.
Let's get some food, I'm starving.
Hey, you know what?
I think I'm gonna stay.
You're kidding, right?
No.
Kai, this car is trash.
What are you gonna do,
drag it out with your bare hands?
I'll figure it out.
Kai, come on, just forget it.
No, I'm gonna stay.
Okay. Um...
Yeah, sure, I guess I could pull my truck,
I don't know, through the trees
and maybe get a winch and--
No, I'm good.
At least let me bring you
to a service station.
You've done enough, it's okay.
I'm good. Just go.
Kai, what's going on? Why don't...?
Why don't you want to come back with me?
- It's not that.
- Then what is it?
You just gave up.
What are you talking about?
I didn't give up shit,
that was taken from me.
That wasn't.
That piece of shit box was nothing.
- You didn't have to kill them.
- They're just fucking bees, Kai.
Right, they mean nothing.
You just threw them away,
that's what you do.
That's what you do.
Fuck you, you don't know me.
You're right, I don't.
Will you let them know
that I can make a payment
when I'm back in a couple of days?
You did, okay. Um...
That's fine. Um...
Yeah, yeah. Um...
Why don't I...? I'll just...
I'll just sell the truck
and it's not a ton of money, but--
No, Mom, don't get--
Hi, Dad.
Yeah.
Uh-huh. Okay, I'll pay you back, okay.
All right. You too.
Can I get you anything?
- Uh, could you just give me a second?
- Oh, yeah, of course, take your time.
Actually, fuck it,
do you have good pancakes?
Uh, is there such a thing as bad pancakes?
Yes, store-bought shit, box shit.
Ma'am, if you'll excuse my French, we have
the best goddamn pancakes in the state.
Made from scratch, local farm-fresh eggs,
butter churned this morning.
My Nana's recipe.
Yeah, I want that.
Oh, fuck.
Hello there.
Nice.
More. More.
- Customers can do this on their own too.
- You're doing great. More.
Just keep going.
It's moving! It's moving! Spike's moving!
Life threatening Spike activity detected.
This is not a drill. You are in danger.
Evacuate immediately.
Do not shelter in place.
Life threatening Spike activity detected.
This is not a drill. You are in danger.
Evacuate immediately.
Life threatening Spike--
Sorry, buddy.
If you didn't want your car jacked up...
you shouldn't have fucking
killed yourself.
Mmm.
Hm. Mm...
- Keep it down!
- Fuck! I did not know you were there.
God.
- Oh, hey, do you have a light?
- Shh!
Okay.
Goddamn.
Motherfucker.
You're not gonna cry, are you?
- What?
- When the end comes.
You're not gonna sit there and bawl
your goddamn eyes out, right?
Hey, lady, can you fucking chill please?
I can't even read my book
and die in peace.
Goddamn it, Kai.
Oh, Kai, you fucking idiot.
Kai? Kai, we gotta go! The Spike's moving!
Kai!
Kai, wake up!
What is this?
Kai?
Kai? The Spike is moving!
The Spike is moving!
Thalia?
- What the hell is going on?
- Where are you?
We're in the Spike or something.
I don't know. Just keep talking.
- I'm trying to find you.
- What are you talking about?
Help!
We gotta go.
Kai? I think there's a way out!
No! No! God! No!
Dave, wake up! Dave, no!
Did he say anything
before he left this morning?
We were supposed
to go on a road trip today.
He wasn't there when I woke up.
Kai.
- Leave me alone.
- Kai! Kai! We gotta get out of here!
Leave me alone!
You sure, Mommy? You sure?
Yeah, just make sure Daddy gets
some dinner on the way home.
Twelve pepperoni pizzas? Got it.
- Pizza party!
- Pizza party! Pizza party! Oh!
- You're so big!
- You're such a dork.
Love you too.
Pizza party! Let's go!
Wait! Don't go!
Kai! Stay there! I'm coming!
So? What do you think?
This is such a fucking stupid car.
I know. I know. It's perfect.
Kai! The Spike is moving! We gotta go!
I can't go with you.
Kai, what's the matter? Tell me, please.
I'm scared.
I'm angry.
How could he do that?
Why? I...
I just can't do it again, Thalia.
Do what?
Care.
I didn't want to,
but now I know you and...
I care about you.
I just can't do it again, okay?
How could it end well
if you never really know someone?
Kai, you're gonna die if you stay here.
Here, somewhere else.
It doesn't matter.
Tell me I'm wrong.
I don't know.
I wish I knew how to help you.
You lied to me.
- When?
- Can I ask you a question?
Does it ever get easier?
What do you want me to tell you?
The truth.
Please.
I can't help you with that.
Why not?
Because I don't know.
Does it get easier?
Yeah, sure. It gets easier.
That's what you're supposed to say, right?
I'm so sorry.
I just wanted to be dead.
To be gone.
Because it never ends.
Every time I remember them,
I lose them again.
How can I be happy
when they're always here?
Just around the corner.
But out of reach.
It never gets easier.
Fuck. Fuck you!
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
It never gets easier.
But sometimes, something happens.
You don't realize it at the time, but...
it changes things.
Kai. Kai.
Maybe it's something you do,
or maybe it's fate.
But you realize...
you're not alone.
You're not alone.
So you coming with me or not?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Just find something that makes you happy.
Hang on to that.
What the fuck?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah. Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe we're still here.
Ow!
What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- Oh, my foot.
Is it stuck on something?
Oh, shit.
What? What is it?
Uh, I'm not really sure
how to explain this one.
Oh, my God.
Okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Just don't move. Just don't move.
No, fuck that.
Break it off or something.
- What? No.
- Yes.
- No.
- What if it spreads?
I give you full consent.
Just rip it out, okay?
- No, I'm not gonna do that.
- Full consent. Just rip it out.
Okay, I'm just gonna--
No, no, no.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
It's okay. It's okay. Um...
- Okay, I'm gonna go get help.
- No, don't you dare.
Don't you dare leave me. Just ding it.
- What?
- Ding it.
Ding it.
Okay. Um...
Ding it, okay.
Uh...
Okay, one...
No, I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't.
I can't. I can't.
- I'm gonna throw up. I'm gonna throw up.
- Okay, screw it.
You know what?
It doesn't even hurt that bad.
- Oh, thank God.
- Weird.
Whoa.
You folks all right? I heard screams.
Yeah, we're okay.
Just, you know, a little shaken up.
Holy shit.
- You're telling me. It got dark so fast.
- Yeah, we know.
Did you two see things?
I was seeing things.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah, for sure.
Well, if you folks are all right,
I think I'm gonna head off.
- Bye.
- I think I'm gonna call my mom.
- I got a lot of stuff to say.
- Cool, man.
Bye.
You're probably gonna have to
take first shift.
- Lead foot and all.
- Yeah, it's fine.
Oh, I am sore all over.
Oh, my gosh.
Wow. That looks weird.
Oh, I hope it didn't get
in my muscles or anything.
Don't wanna get cancer.
- What?
- Nothing.
I get it. My nubs are weird.
No, it's not that.
You have nice calves.
I like calves, and you have nice ones.
- What?
- Okay.
- These do it for you?
- Yes, unfortunately.
Okay.
I thought it was my charm.
- Whoa.
- Whoa. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Definitely not your charm.
Well, I like your calves too.
I've never looked at your calves,
but if they're half as nice as your ass...
Oh, my God.
You know what?
Never mind. It is your charm.
Thanks for coming back for me.
Thanks for having nice calves.
- You're making it weird.
- Yeah.
Hey, look.
Are those your bees?
Who knows?
But I'm going to get these buzz boys
a new home.
You ladies keep bringing friends,
I'm gonna have to get us another box.
- I thought you were working this morning.
- I was.
Then I got an emergency call from somebody
saying they needed some coffee.
Oh, and breakfast?
I don't know.
I'll have to examine the patient first.
You're gross.
Did you drive the ambulance here?
- Are you even allowed to do that?
- Shut up, narc.
- You want breakfast or what?
- Yes, I want breakfast.
- Just let me clean up.
- Yeah, I was gonna say.
Excuse me.
That is the sweat of a working woman.
Smell it.
- No.
- Smell it.
- No, I'm okay.
- Smell my glory!
- Smell it!
- Get off me. Get off me.
You're absolutely nuts.
I was kidding, by the way.
Oh, really?
Yes, I've been working all day unlike you.
I have been working.
You smell how much I've been working!
- No, no!
- Smell it.
- You're so terrible!
- You know you want it!